webfortunemaster.com 2013-08-05

# Web Fortune Master

**Effective Date: May 9, 2012**

Thank you for visiting the Web Fortune Master website located at webfortunemaster.com (the “Site”) The Site is owned and operated by Web Fortune Master ("we," or "us"). Web Fortune Master has created this Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") in order to keep users informed as to how we gather information and how that information is disseminated. We understand the importance that Internet users place on privacy, and we have designed our service with this in mind. Information

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personal information that we collect when you: (a) access or use our Site; and/or (b) register, or attempt to register, on the Site. The types of personally identifiable information that we collect at the Site, during registration and when you make a purchase may include, without limitation, any of the following: (i) full name; (ii) street address; (iii) e-mail address; (iv) telephone number (home and work); (v) date of birth; and (vi) credit card information. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, item (vi) in the preceding sentence shall be considered “Sensitive Information.” In addition, we may request information about your use of, or interest in, the types of products and services offered by the third party sellers with whom we have partnered to offer you the products and services available at the Site.

For purposes of compliance with the California Financial Privacy Act, the Vermont Consumer Protection Act, 8 V.S.A. 10202 and North Dakota Century Code §§ 6.08.1-01 to 6-08.1-08, if you are a resident of the State of California, Vermont or North Dakota and would like to opt-out from the disclosure of your personal information to any third-party for marketing purposes, please Click Here. Please be advised that where California, Vermont or North Dakota residents opt-out from permitting their personal information to be shared, such individuals may still receive selected offers directly from us, in accordance with the law.

### IP Addresses

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Site and to prevent fraud. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information, as well as to offer you products and services.

### Cookies

We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. Cookies are text files that we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies do not personally identify you in any way.

### Sharing of Information

Web Fortune Master uses the information described above to tailor our content and help our advertisers and third party marketers better understand the demographic profile of our Site’s users. The personally identifiable information that you submit to Web Fortune Master remains your property, however, by submitting that information to Web Fortune Masteryou grant Web Fortune Masterthe right to use that information as set forth herein.

We may use your personal information (other than the Sensitive Information) and/or transfer the personal information you supply on the Site (other than the Sensitive Information) to other third party businesses, subject to applicable state and federal law, for any legal purpose including, without limitation to: (a) bring selected retail opportunities and promotional offers to you via direct mail marketing, e-mail marketing, telemarketing and/or online banner advertising; (b) when necessary, to receive a product or service that you may have ordered from such third party while using the Site or when responding to offers provided by Web Fortune Master; (c) tracking compliance with our Terms and Conditions located at ("Terms and Conditions"); (d) SMS text-based marketers (where permitted by applicable law); and (e) for validation, suppression, content improvement and feedback purposes. These third party businesses may include providers of direct marketing services and applications, including look up and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation, and e-mail marketing. By permitting Web Fortune Master to collect this information, you will be able to receive free information on products and services that may be of interest to you. We use contact information collected from our Site to send you information about us, to keep you informed of products and services that may be of interest to you, as well as to service your account with us should you place an order. In addition, you agree that we may contact you with updates and/or any other information that we may deem appropriate for you to receive in connection with your account and/or the Site.

We also use this information to personalize your experience with Web Fortune Master. Contact information is also used to reach you, when necessary, regarding the use of our Site, products and/or services. By submitting your e-mail address at the Site, you agree to receive e-mail marketing from Web Fortune Master and our third party advertisers. We only send e-mail marketing to individuals that have agreed to receive e-mail from Web Fortune Master and to individuals that have otherwise agreed, on third party websites, to receive e-mail marketing from other companies. Web Fortune Master does not send unsolicited commercial e-mail. As a result, certain statutes requiring particular formatting for unsolicited commercial e-mail may not be applicable to the commercial e-mail that is sent by Web Fortune Master. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we will not send you any e-mail marketing, or allow any third party to send you e-mail marketing, from which you cannot unsubscribe.

You may choose to stop receiving future communications regarding products and services we may offer to you (see the "Opt-Out/Unsubscribe" section below), however we may be required to contact you thereafter regarding any order or purchase that you may make while on this site. You may choose to stop receiving future communications regarding products and services we may offer to you (see the "Opt-Out/Unsubscribe" section below), however we may be required to contact you thereafter regarding any order or purchase that you may make while on this Site.

In addition, you agree that by submitting your e-mail address at the Site and/or registering for the products and/or service offered herein, such act constitutes a purchase, an inquiry and/or an application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule, 16 CFR §310 et seq. (the "ATSR") and any applicable state and local do-not-call regulations. Notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal Trade Commission's Do-Not-Call List, or an applicable state do-not-call list, we retain the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the ATSR and the applicable state regulations. Moreover, by registering with, or requesting information from, a third party advertiser at or through the Site, such action shall constitute a purchase, an inquiry and/or an application with the respective third party advertiser for purposes of the ATSR and any applicable state and local do-not-call regulations and you may be contacted via e-mail, direct mail and/or telemarketing by such third party advertiser in accordance with the ATSR and the applicable state regulations.

In addition, you agree that by submitting your mobile telephone number at the Site, you agree to receive mobile marketing including, but not limited to, text-message based marketing, from us and our third party advertisers and marketers (where, and to the extent that, such marketing is permitted by applicable law). As such, notwithstanding that your mobile telephone number may be listed on state and/or federal Do-Not-Call registries, we retain the right to contact you via text-message based marketing in accordance with applicable state and federal law. Further, you agree that we reserve the right to share, sell, rent, lease and/or otherwise distribute your mobile telephone and other mobile data with/to any third-party for any and all non-marketing uses permitted by this Privacy Policy and applicable law. We do not control, and are not responsible for, the practices of our advertisers or third party marketers. We will never disclose any Sensitive Information to any third-party marketers or other non-governmental entity. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may: (i) share the fact that we have Sensitive Information on file for specific users of the Site but we will not share your specific Sensitive Information with such third parties without your prior informed consent; (ii) share your Sensitive Information with consumer credit agencies; and (iii) disclose your Sensitive Information to third party processors for the sole purpose of effectuating transactions that you enter into at the Site. We may also disclose your personally identifiable and/or Sensitive Information: (A) to a governmental entity if so ordered by a court of law, to comply with the local, state and federal laws; (B) where otherwise required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our Site; or (C) if we are sold or acquired.

### Other Websites

This Site, and/or the products and/or services offered herein, may contain links to other websites. We do not endorse, nor are we responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. The entities that advertise and/or place links at the Site including, but not limited to, these websites, are independent third parties and are not affiliated with us. Additionally, certain components of our products and/or services may be provided by partners. In these circumstances: (a) you will be redirected to the applicable third party partner’s website after you have completed the applicable application page; (b) either we will collect and send your personal information to the third party partner, or such third party partner will itself collect your personal information, in connection with completing your purchase from such third party partner; and (c) your purchase will subject you to such third party partner’s privacy policy.

### Third-Party Offers

Web Fortune Master provides its' users with the opportunity to receive special offers, products and/or services from us and third parties. By providing your information to us during any of the Web Fortune Master information collection processes, you are providing affirmative consent to receive offers that we feel may be of interest to you from third parties. Furthermore, if you indicate the desire to receive certain offers, products or services from a specific vendor during the applicable information collection process, your personally identifiable information that was provided to us during the information collection process will be shared with the applicable third party so that such third party may provide their product or service to you and so that you do not have to complete another information collection form to purchase or receive that product or service.

### Security

All collected information is stored in a technically and physically secure environment. When our registration/application process prompts users to enter Sensitive Information, and when we store and transmit such Sensitive Information, that information is encrypted and is protected with SSL encryption software. While we use SSL encryption to protect Sensitive Information online, we also take reasonable measures to protect all other user information online and off-line. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems. All of our users' information, not just Sensitive Information, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personal information. Furthermore, access to this information is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public. Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all user information. Employees not adhering to our firm policies established in writing are subject to disciplinary action. Please note that any attempt to breach the security of the network, our servers, databases or other hardware or software supporting this Site or other websites under the control of Web Fortune Master constitutes a crime punishable by law. We will turn over to authorities, any and all evidence relating to a potential breach of security or other abuse against the network, servers, databases or other such supporting equipment or software. In compliance with applicable federal and state laws, we shall notify you in the event that we learn of an information security breach with respect to your personal information. You will be notified via e-mail in the event of such a breach. Please be advised that notice may be delayed in order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of network damage, and to engage in remedial measures.

### Children's Guidelines

We take special steps to safeguard the privacy of children. It is important for children to get permission from their parents before accessing or supplying any personal information to our site. We will never knowingly collect personally identifiable information from people under eighteen (18) years of age.

### Opt-Out/Unsubscribe

Web Fortune Master , and our third party advertisers, may maintain separate e-mail lists for different purposes. If you wish to end your e-mail subscription to a particular list, you must follow the instructions contained in each e-mail correspondence that you receive from Web Fortune Master or the applicable third party advertiser to unsubscribe from that particular list. To unsubscribe from all e-mail advertising please visit our Op-Out/Unsubscribe page, click here or send a letter to 

#### 50 West Broadway  
Salt Lake City, UT 84101.

### Changes in Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change or update this privacy policy at any time by posting a notice on our Site that we are changing our privacy policy. If the manner in which we use personally identifiable information changes, we will notify you by: (a) posting the changes as a start-up screen prior to your subsequent use of the products and/or service offered herein; (b) sending the modified policy to the users via email; (c) placing a link to the modified policy on our website; or (d) by any other reasonable means acceptable under applicable state and federal law. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. At any time that you do not agree with the changes, you must opt out from receiving future communications from us (see the "Opt-Out/Unsubscribe" section above). Failure to opt out after notice of any such changes constitutes an affirmative acknowledgement and acceptance by you of the modified Privacy Policy.

### Contacting the Site

We read every message sent to us and try to reply promptly to each one. This information is used to respond directly to your questions and comments. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices of Web Fortune Master, please feel free to contact us at:

#### 50 West Broadway  
Salt Lake City, UT 84101  
Email:support@webfortunemaster.com
